freestockphotos.biz 2017-06-09

# Free Stock Photos | Privacy Policy

We take your right to privacy seriously. This Policy discloses the privacy practices for this website and other GSE-Media web properties (the "Site"). In reviewing this Policy, you can expect to be notified of: what personally identifiable information of yours is collected; the organization collecting the information; how the information is used; with whom the information may be shared; what choices are available to you regarding collection, use and distribution of the information; the kind and efficacy of security procedures that are in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of information under the licensee's control; and your ability to access, correct, and/or delete information you previously provided. Questions regarding this Policy should be directed to GSE-Media. To return to the Site, please use the "Back" button on your browser. 

**Does GSE-Media ask for/require/gather personal information?**

To make use of certain features on the Site (such as free emails and other interactive forums) visitors must register and provide certain information as part of the registration process. We may ask, for example, for your name, email address, sex, age, and zip code, and information regarding particular issues of interest to you. This list is not exhaustive and may include other information of a personal character. Supplying such information is entirely voluntary. If, however, you do not supply the information we need, we may be unable to provide you with services we make available to other visitors to the Site. Of course, even if you want to remain completely anonymous, you are still free to take advantage of the wealth of content available on the Site by registering as a guest or by not registering. 

In addition, we invoke a standard feature of browser software, called a "cookie," to assign each visitor a unique, random number or other data. This "cookie", if you will, resides on your computer. The cookie does not actually identify the visitor, just the computer that a visitor uses to access our site. Unless you voluntarily identify yourself (through registration, for example), we will not know who you are, even if we assign a cookie to your computer. The only personal information a cookie can contain is information you supply, and a cookie cannot read data off of your hard drive. Our advertisers may also assign their own cookies to your browser, a process over which we have no control. 

Lastly, our web servers automatically collect limited information about your computer's connection to the Internet, including your IP address, when you visit the Site. Your IP address is a number that lets computers attached to the Internet know where to send you data -- such as the web pages you view. Your IP address does not identify you personally. 

**How does GSE-Media use this information?**

The information you supply will help us to offer you more personalized features, to tailor the Site to your interests, and to make it more interesting and meaningful to you. The more you tell us about yourself, the more value we can offer you. For example, we cannot send you email alerting you to a new service we are offering or news that may interest you if you do not tell us your interests and give us your email address. 

We also provide aggregated demographic information in summary form (names are never included) to our advertisers. For example, we might say that 65% of our surfers are women. 

We may use cookies to help us deliver a better, more personalized service. For example, we may use cookies to avoid repeatedly showing you the same ad during a single visit, and to track the pages on the Site visited by our users. Of course, you can set your browser not to accept cookies, but if you do, you may not be able to take advantage of the personalized features enjoyed by other visitors to the Site. 

We use your IP address to deliver our web pages to you upon request, to tailor the Site to the interests of our users, and to measure traffic within the Site. 

We will not use the information to contact you in any way unless you affirmatively provide your permission. For example, if you join a newsletter program we will send you regular email updates. If you enter and win a contest, we will contact you to send you your prize. And if you indicate to us that you would like to receive offers or other information from other companies, we may provide your name and demographic information to companies interested in contacting people with interests like yours. 

**Third Party Advertising**

We use various third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please click [here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/optout_nonppii.asp). 

For more information about individual adnetworks and their corresponding privacy policies, please check below:

**Third Party Cookies**

In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique “cookie” on your browser. 

**Does GSE-Media provide my information to anyone else for email, direct mail, or other purposes?**

We provide information to our sponsors and advertisers -- to help them understand our audience and confirm the value of advertising on the Site. This information is provided in the form of aggregated statistics and demographics on traffic to various pages within the Site. 

The sponsors and advertisers will not contact you in any way unless you affirmatively provide your permission. For example, if you request information or other items from a specific advertiser, we will provide your name and demographic information to that advertiser so that the advertiser can respond to your request. And if you indicate to us that you would like to receive offers or other information from other companies, we may provide your name and demographic information to companies interested in contacting people with interests like yours. 

In addition, we allow access to information to third-party technical service providers, but only to the extent necessary to provide you with the applicable service. In such instances, the third-party is bound by this Policy. 

Lastly, obviously we will disclose information about you in our possession as required by applicable law or legal process. 

**Inherent risks of the Internet**

All information gathered on the Site is encrypted for storage within a GSE-Media-controlled database. However, as effective as encryption technology is, no security system is impenetrable. We cannot guarantee the security of our database, nor can we guarantee that information you supply will not be intercepted while being transmitted to us over the Internet. Of course, any information you include in a message you post to any message board, forum or other public posting area is available to anyone with Internet access. If you do not want people to know your email address, for example, do not include it in any message you post publicly. 

**A note regarding the privacy of children**

Children should always get permission from their parents before sending any information about themselves (such as their names, email addresses, and phone numbers) over the Internet, to us or to anyone else. We will not knowingly allow anyone under 13 to register with the Site or to access those features that require registration. 

**Changes to this Policy**

The Web is an evolving medium. If we need to change our privacy policy at some point in the future, we will post the changes before they take effect. Of course, our use of information gathered while the current policy is in effect will always be consistent with the current policy, even if we change that policy later.
